import { Question } from "../App";

export const goblinData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the main character's name in 'Goblin' who is also known as the Goblin?",
            "options": ["Kim Shin", "Wang Yeo", "Lee Dong-wook", "Joo Seong-ha"],
            "answer": "Kim Shin"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the curse that Kim Shin suffers from in the series?",
            "options": ["Immortality", "Amnesia", "Poverty", "Isolation"],
            "answer": "Immortality"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the Goblin's bride, destined to end his immortality?",
            "options": ["Ji Eun-tak", "Kim Go-eun", "Wang Yeo", "Yoo Deok-hwa"],
            "answer": "Ji Eun-tak"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the Grim Reaper in the series who is a key character?",
            "options": ["Wang Yeo", "Kim Shin", "Deok-hwa", "The King"],
            "answer": "Wang Yeo"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the profession of Ji Eun-tak?",
            "options": ["High school student", "College student", "Teacher", "Singer"],
            "answer": "High school student"
        },
        {
            "question": "What significant event happens to Ji Eun-tak on her 19th birthday?",
            "options": ["She meets the Goblin", "She finds a hidden treasure", "She moves to a new city", "She receives a magical power"],
            "answer": "She meets the Goblin"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the Goblin's loyal servant and also a powerful figure in his own right?",
            "options": ["Deok-hwa", "Grim Reaper", "Sunny", "The King"],
            "answer": "Deok-hwa"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the Goblin's love interest, who also happens to be a supernatural being?",
            "options": ["Sunny", "Ji Eun-tak", "Wang Yeo", "The Queen"],
            "answer": "Sunny"
        },
        {
            "question": "What item is crucial to breaking the Goblin's curse?",
            "options": ["A magical sword", "A special ring", "A book of spells", "A destined bride"],
            "answer": "A destined bride"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Wang Yeo (the Grim Reaper) struggle with throughout the series?",
            "options": ["His lost memories", "His immortality", "His love for Sunny", "His role in the afterlife"],
            "answer": "His lost memories"
        }
    ]
